Kenneth Dunn

kmdunn5@gmail.com | 860-608-2216 | Brooklyn, New York | GitHub | Portfolio

OVERVIEW

Eager & experienced coding bootcamp graduate with a keen knack for finding & fixing problems that others might miss! I am an attentive individual with 8 years of professional experience recently turned Full Stack Web Developer. Prioritizing scalability from the beginning has been a focus in my process. As a meticulous Stagehand, I learned the importance of efficiency & precision in each task I tackle.

Collaborative & forthcoming, I foster open & clear communication across teams & disciplines. Aiming to develop technical solutions that will make a positive impact on lives, I am eager to join a team of goal-oriented professionals.

TECHNOLOGIES

LCIINOLOGILS			
LANGUAGES	DATABASES	LIBRARIES & FRAMEWORKS	<u>OTHER</u>
HTML	 PostgreSQL 	JQuery	 Object Oriented Programming
CSS	ORM	Node.js	• Git
 Javascript 	 MongoDB 	React	 GitHub
Python	 Mongoose 	Express.js	 RESTful Routing
Ruby	ODM	Flask	JSON

RELATED EXPERIENCE

General Assembly, Online Bootcamp

JAN 2021 - APRIL 2021

Software Engineering Immersive, (Student)

- Developed 4 applications using several programming languages, libraries & frameworks
- Built familiarity with frontend & backend development, backend data processing applications, provisioning infrastructure
- Established ideation & planning of app features

PROJECTS

Zookies Dookies - GitHub

- Stack: Python, Flask, React, PostgreSQL (RESTful server)
- With a robust database focused on future, this app allows a user to add dogs they are taking care of & track different health requirements

Board Game Catalogue — GitHub

- Stack: Node.js, Express, EJS, MongoDB (MVC & RESTful server)
- Using authentication, allows a user to create board games & add those to different lists of theirs, programmatically populating those lists on their home page

Plant Buddi - GitHub

- Stack: Node.js, Express, React, MongoDB (RESTful server)
- Using an external API, allows users to search for their plants & add them to the tracker, while adding information that would be required to keep their plants healthy

Black-Jack-Black — GitHub

- Stack: HTML5, CSS, Javascript
- Allows the user to play Blackjack against a programmed opponent, handling logic for math, betting, & dealing

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Brooklyn Academy of Music • Brooklyn, NY

MAY 2013 — PRESENT

Audio Stagehand

- Led team of up to 15 staff in pre-show set up & transitional set up during shows
- Oversaw wireless equipment installations & operations
- Coordinated across 4 departments for optimal workflow efficiency
- Managed assignments in the audio department for 100+ live shows of varying styles
- Provided time-sensitive systemic solutions prior to & during a show, including programming & implementation
- Created & maintained a trusting rapport with 100+ visiting talent & technicians that fostered reliable performances daily
- Oversaw installation, testing & implementation of various systems, requiring proficiency in hardware integration

EDUCATION

Hofstra University, New York

Bachelor Of Arts with Honors, Awarded Radio Senior

Major: Radio Production & Studies | Minor: Communications

SEPT 2008 — MAY 2012